<resources>
    <string name="app_name">bookWorm</string>
    <string name="add_to_shelf">Add to Shelf</string>
    <string name="for_you">For You</string>
    <string name="twilight">Seventeen-year-old Bella Swan hugs her Mom goodbye in Phoenix. She boards the plane that will take her to the rainiest place in the U.S.: the tiny town of Forks, Washington, where Bella will live with her dad, Charlie. Bella knows she’s going to hate Forks, but things start to look up when Charlie picks her up and reveals that he already bought Bella an old Chevy truck from his friend Billy Black.</string>
    <string name="nightingale">In 1995, a terminally ill older woman living in Oregon reflects upon her past and the secrets that she has kept from her family. In an old trunk in her attic, she looks upon a French identity card bearing the name “Juliette Gervaise.” Decades earlier in France, two sisters, Vianne and Isabelle, are abandoned by their father after the death of their mother. The older sister, Vianne, marries her childhood sweetheart, Antoine, and after several miscarriages, they have a daughter named Sophie. The three live together in peace in their home, named Le Jardin, in the rural town of Carriveau. </string>
    <string name="fault_on_our_stars">Seventeen-year-old Hazel Grace Lancaster reluctantly attends a cancer patients\' support group at her mother’s behest. Because of her cancer, she uses a portable oxygen tank to breathe properly. In one of the meetings she catches the eye of a teenage boy, and through the course of the meeting she learns the boy’s name is Augustus Waters. He\'s there to support their mutual friend, Isaac. Isaac had a tumor in one eye that he had removed, and now he has to have his other eye taken out as well. After the meeting ends, Augustus approaches Hazel and tells her she looks like Natalie Portman in V for Vendetta. He invites Hazel to his house to watch the movie, and while hanging out, the two discuss their experiences with cancer. Hazel reveals she has thyroid cancer that has spread to her lungs. Augustus had osteosarcoma, but he is now cancer free after having his leg amputated.</string>
    <string name="hunger_games">Katniss Everdeen wakes up on the day of the reaping, when the tributes are chosen who will take part in the Hunger Games. Her mother and little sister, Prim, sleep nearby. Her father died in a mine explosion years earlier. She goes hunting in the woods outside her district, District 12, with Gale, her best friend. That night, at the reaping ceremony, the mayor gives a speech describing how the governments of North America collapsed and the country of Panem rose up in their place. A war ensued between the Capitol and the districts. The Capitol won, and as a reminder of their defeat, the Capitol holds the Hunger Games every year. The mayor then introduces Haymitch Abernathy, District 12’s only living Hunger-Games winner, and he’s so drunk he ends up falling in his own vomit.</string>
    <string name="great_gasby">Nick Carraway, a young man from Minnesota, moves to New York in the summer of 1922 to learn about the bond business. He rents a house in the West Egg district of Long Island, a wealthy but unfashionable area populated by the new rich, a group who have made their fortunes too recently to have established social connections and who are prone to garish displays of wealth. Nick’s next-door neighbor in West Egg is a mysterious man named Jay Gatsby, who lives in a gigantic Gothic mansion and throws extravagant parties every Saturday night.</string>
    <string name="double_sin">When Hercule Poirot takes a holiday to Ebermouth with his friend Hastings, he didn\'t expect it would turn into a case. But when a young woman named Mary Durrant asks Poirot for help after miniatures that were mailed to a client go missing, the great detective springs into action. Were the miniatures simply misplaced or deliberately stolen? And if stolen, by whom? Poirot must rely on his "little grey cells" to unravel the mystery and identify the true culprit.</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="my_library">My Library</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
</resources>